I thought I was done
when I hung up the mask
I hung it up for good
I believed it was all over
that the world has truly gotten better
that it
understood
but it's never over
there are always more eggs to crack
more yolks to throw
I'm not the hero the server ones
I'm not the hero this server needs
I am not the hero This Server deserves
[Music]
but I'm the only one that's got
foreign
[Music]
hello everybody or welcome back to
another episode of hermitcraft as you
might have been able to tell poultry man
has come out of retirement now we still
don't know who poultry man is
but he's definitely made a comeback and
something has also appeared in my base
let's go and have a quick look shall we
so Mumbo has left me a little something
something with obsidian here it says if
you use a pickaxe on these I will know
hmm
he's not gonna know
I anyway I have a better idea I I have a
I have a really good idea well I'm not
going to use a pickaxe to do this I'm
going to use a bit of mumbo's own
methods if I'm honest
[Laughter]
thanks for my Trident and for breaking
my fists
wait can you see me I didn't use a pick
he I can't get punished for that I
didn't use a pick I used a clever method
I I have to leave this obsidian here
forever but I didn't use a pickaxe
you've lied me
where is he where is he I'm gonna find
him he's here he can see me where is he
he's not looking through a window ah
what are you doing he was supposed to
open up all of those chests in that
flying box but he didn't do it he didn't
do it he went straight down and he
missed all of the the funny jokes that
we made he says we'll see how iscal
fares well I'm down to help
he was spying on me through this window
he could oh he was watching me through
here
sneaky man that sneaky little mustache
[Laughter]
he's gonna go and add some extra
obsidian to iskal's one I plan to AFK
that all night but you arrived just as I
was putting the weights on my keyboard
I can use the I can actually use the
pickaxe now that he's gone he won't even
notice that was really cheeky that was
really cheeky
I used my Superior Minecraft knowledge
I think I think that is scales not quite
gonna get away with it though but two
shulker boxes full of
oh
there's obsidian in the shulker boxes
called bloodstones oh he's just I just
say though green what I saw you go down
a water elevator and then a chicken man
appeared moments later it wasn't me it
was the man in the chicken costume I
don't know what he's on about
so I've got rid of that and I've opened
up the way to the new poultry cave so
this is what I time lapsed briefly and
I'll go and show you the inside so I had
to like there's water behind all of this
so I had to make this little hole here
this is going to be the secret entrance
to the poultry cave if we drop on
through
this is what I've made now this is
basically all decoration here because
you don't really see this so it was a
bit of a waste of time but you can see
the Giant Egg that I have made in the
middle of the cave which actually I'm
pretty I'm pretty happy with the shape
of this it probably could have been a
bit you know longer here I think the
bottom should have been thinner but you
know as as far as eggs go I think it's
there's not too bad I did it the first
time so let's go and have a look inside
so this is where poultry man keeps his
outfit
right in here and I haven't actually
made a way up or or down yet but I'm
gonna work on that now but one of the
things that I really want to do is have
a full supply of chicken eggs at all
times I'm going to create basically a
chicken farm inside here two of them
each side and this should provide
poultry man with enough chicken eggs to
last a very long time I I oh I didn't go
please go back in
please
go back in
come on come on come on come on come on
okay well I'll I'll have to fill that up
in a minute I haven't got enough eggs on
me right now to to fill this up oh dear
all right I've stockpiled up on some
eggs let's get this chicken farm on the
road we don't want enough we don't want
so many chickens that it's gonna lag but
we want to make sure that we have an
infinite supply of eggs now you don't
actually need that many as we know from
when poultry man filled up the tubes
from the mailing system you don't
actually need a lot of chickens to
provide you with the kind of eggs that
we're talking about
that is more than enough chickens on
that side
now we just need some more on this side
if it starts lagging too much I will get
rid of some of them but these guys are
Gonna Keep poultry man well stocked and
it's fair to say that a couple of them
missed the mark but we might as well
keep a few of them down here anyway so
this is really really cool I feel like I
could put a couple of banners here with
some sort of egg thing I don't really
know how to make banners too well but if
I could make like an egg Banner that
would be so cool so there he is
cold tree man himself the real question
is who's the man behind the chicken
costume
all right we need to make a little
entrance for this now
so I've got a few sticky pistons and I
think I know how to make these I I think
I'm I'm testing my very basic Redstone
skills here
I think that's pretty much the
no that's pretty much it like us most of
what you need right just two three
sticky pistons and then I've got a I've
got a I've got a well I've got a
redstone this stuff
the mechanism that I plan on using for
this is fairly simple but we're going to
need some more space I think there's too
much water behind here at the moment I'm
gonna need some more space for Redstone
so what I need to do is figure out the
best place to put the trip wire in
because I also figured out you can use
this tripwire hook thing underneath the
floor so the idea here is that I'm just
going to throw the Trident at the floor
it's going to go through and Trigger it
so if I go something like this boom it
will open up the hole in the floor I
just need to make sure actually I might
try and make sure that it's close enough
here that I can stand let's say here and
Trigger it from here that would be I
think that would be the best really if I
know exactly where this is and then I
can just throw the Trident down I think
that will look the best
so let's try and put the mechanism
right
here
all right let's give this one a go I
think I might have it figured out
[Music]
that's a definite no
[Laughter]
it's not very clean at all I can't
exactly ask someone to come and make
this better for me because otherwise
they're gonna they're gonna know who
poultry man is but I mean no one knows
who poultry man is so I don't know I
can't I can't risk it I can't risk
poultry man is a close friend of mine
and I can't you know I can't I can't
betray him I've already lost it so here
hold on do I go like this
so if I throw this at the floor
that should give me the drop down that I
need into the poultry egg
this is brilliant absolutely brilliant
the only yeah I've I've forgotten about
the exit out no this may have to do I'm
not gonna lie this may have to just be
it as long as it works that's the main
thing
um I'm not too fussed about it being the
absolute best Redstone in the world
but obviously I I do wish it was a
little bit better than it is
and we're all covered up so in theory
this is this is how it should go I'm
gonna stand on the Block where it is I
throw the Trident at the floor
unlucky that time now
I thought I had this
ah there we go so right I throw it
directly in the Block in front of me
and I fall down I do get punched a
little bit by the Pistons because
they're too quick but then I fall down
into the poultry cave and I can get well
I mean Poetry Man can then have access
to his suit whoever poultry man may be
hey
this is this is excellent we don't have
any eggs yet but they're still little
baby chicks so that's to be expected I'm
sure that one day they'll be there'll be
big Checkers and they'll be able to
provide the eggs that poultry man needs
the next thing to work on is how do I
get out of here
because right now I guess there is this
like I can use my um maintenance exit
which is through this whole hick all
right let's try it again I'm getting
better at flying through one wide holes
but not perfect yet in other news you
guys warned me the day the literally the
day that this happened you guys warned
me that if I let Jack skellabone out of
his little cage he would go wandering
into that portal and go missing you are
absolutely correct almost within the
hour Jack skellabone went and wandered
straight in here I have no idea where
he's gone
uh he might be wandering around in here
potentially but he also could have gone
for a Wonder
off this ledge
or any other ledge
in fact
I think Jack skellabone number two
is gone
but if his wish was to be free
then I think that Jack skellabone should
be free
if anybody sees him
please do contact his owner immediately
the thing is I didn't really use him he
kind of was just trapped in my base
which uh
I think I think Freedom possibly would
suit him a bit better
now in other news the green head Hunt is
now concluded absolutely finito so we
can get rid of all these signs because
it is now done
I need to now organize to meet up with
everybody that participated there may
still be one or two green heads lying
around and I'm not gonna know whether
they pick them up or not but I'm not
gonna care too much if they do it the
deadline is now but over the next couple
of days I'm going to be counting up
everybody's uh head count and then yeah
we're going to be performing a head
count and then the winner will get this
luxuriously what Excuse excuse me oh man
the winner as I was saying will get this
luxurious box of goodies gravel nether
quartz sand fireworks wither skulls and
diamonds and then Korean will help you
with any prank I really should have put
in here a clause that said I will not
help you prank me
so that's a really decent box of goodies
in my opinion you've got well not to
mention all those shulker boxes so let's
put that now there seems to have been
quite a lot of dealings going on between
the Hermits about trying to find a way
to get the most heads but
this has been a really fun event I hope
that I can come up with something like
this in the future as well that um that
I can I can be a part of now a few of
you might be wondering what was
the Riddle That I put here because a lot
of you actually didn't get it right I
only saw two or three comments out of
everybody that actually got it right now
if you remember what it said I because I
I genuinely I don't actually remember
what it's said I got rid of the signs
but what it said was you need to go up
to the build height it basically said
you need to go to the Limit now the the
height limit is all the way up here
so it told you the y coordinate then it
said go to the base that's the color of
snow my base is mostly white so it meant
my base and to give you an extra Hint it
says if you stand in the middle you will
fall so that should be enough to point
you towards my base now most people went
down and fell down there and thought
that it was down there but it didn't
actually tell you to fall it just says
if you go down the middle you will fall
but it actually said to go up to the
limit which is up here
now it also said where there are there
is two but never three up here there is
one two three blocks one two three but
only two on this Tower so where there is
two but never three so there's three
blocks on top of those ones I actually
added those three for the clue and I
removed one here for this one so this
should be where you ended up and if you
knocked in the block and you fell down
and someone found where all of the heads
were and they actually left a sign
saying I think you'll find that it was
35 and not 33. so yeah that was that's
really good someone did find it but I
checked this place multiple times and it
actually took several days for it to get
found which I'm pretty proud of it was a
more complicated clue and some people
were absolutely losing their marbles
over trying to find where it is and I
think that was that was pretty fun and
as always I've already run out of
rockets
smooth smooth
so it's only been a few days since I
created my stockpile of rockets and I'm
piling through them at all times and
there's been several rocket shops pop up
in the last few days so we're gonna go
and buy them at a house and homes
straight away I feel absolutely no
allegiance to any one shop Tango so if
you can provide me with cheap Rockets
I'll buy them ah man someone's already
bought all the rocket boxes so the
convex are selling 12 diamonds for one
rocket box there's a look at this see
all of the boxes have been done
and one Diamond per stack oh these are
premium Rockets flight duration three
you say now what does that mean does it
mean it gives you a boost for longer
well I've got a I've got to try it out
premium Rockets
exploding Rockets oh I'm being oh I'm
pick any 20 for one diamond oh oh my
goodness I need I'm being spoiled for
Choice here
let's go and try out these fresh new
rockets so duration three does that mean
you just get a boost for that much
longer so I'm at 62 now if I go straight
up with one rocket I end up at one three
six
if I take a duration one rocket
I end up at 116. that's like
that is not worth the the extra money
for a 15 blocks that's uh not that great
I take my rocket science very seriously
okay guys
so what do these do
oh they they hurt
what
no I don't I don't want that
cool guys don't look at explosions
what if you like spam them
okay spamming them was a bad idea
spamming them was definitely a bad idea
they really do a lot of damage okay well
we won't be buying the premium fireworks
because they just don't seem worth it
however there's another shop that has
popped up mumbo's Rocket Shop and it it
was here
mumbo's rocket shot has really taken off
does that mean it's somewhere else now
has it popped up elsewhere oh no no it's
really taken off oh it's literally up
here
how did I not see this flying around so
much
mumbo's defective Rocket Shop Tango
found out
shot put Tech to the skies
let's buy Rockets I tell you what can I
just swap out a shulker box sorry Tango
but if you want to stay on top of the
Rocket game you've got to offer a better
price oh
that that must hurt look at that that's
the first time I've seen this place with
absolutely no diamonds in I think Tech
to the skies is gonna end up broke if he
doesn't do something because I'm gonna
put my money where the Rockets are you
know there we go nine diamonds in there
and we've got a another fresh shulker
box full of fireworks you know one day
I'm gonna make my own creeper Farm
and one day I'm gonna make my own
creeper farm and my own Reed farm and I
will catch up to everyone else but
while Rockets are so cheap and I'm I'm
like the best customer for Rockets I oh
ow I I don't think I really need to it's
a lot of time spent for a few diamonds
cast but man I really get through these
things oh wait there's a sign here
because you broke my indicator you got
mail well Mumbo you could have fixed it
the only reason I well I I moved it I
just I need help wait why have I got six
Rockets thanks for your help on the farm
your hourly rate was 10 Rockets an hour
you helped for half an hour so here plus
one to keep you sweet really that I I I
helped him make that creeper farm and
this was my payment it's actually been a
pretty lonely day on the server there's
not that many people oh yeah
now because it is the first of December
I will be wearing my Christmas skin from
now on and you might be wondering why
I'm placing snow here I'm not changing
the floor of my base although actually
that does look pretty good oh no yeah I
remember now the the sea lanterns will
break it what I'm doing is I'm getting
myself a load of snowballs because the
winter event from this point forward is
about a snowball fight so you'll see the
in the tablets there's a zero next to my
name and scars so the idea here is that
you get a point every time you hit a
unique hermit with a snowball so we're
gonna go and get ours from scar right
now but I needed to collect snowballs
now I'm gonna play this a little bit
differently from everybody else I think
because I'm going to have a snowball
with everybody's name on it
we got scar Mumbo eskau
cub
excise Zoom
stress
Cleo
impulse
Tango
Ren
doc
jevin
false
TFC
Wells night
and python now I think that's everybody
that is currently active on the server
so if I've missed anyone I do apologize
it's quite a lot of people to remember
and I am still the new guy so do bear
that in mind now we're going to create a
little bit of a Hit List here now I have
definitely don't have enough item frames
oh no that doesn't count okay so that is
everybody we have python TFC yeah we
just went through all that so scar is
the only one online so we need to go and
get him with this snowball and hopefully
that will get us our very first snowball
point it's so easy to accidentally hit
people with these we need to be super
careful he's just told me that he's busy
making stuff at the golf course so
scarce scar
you can't tell me where you are you make
it too easy bro oh my goodness
this place looks amazing that is
absolutely is that floating sand I I get
distracted too easily look at that what
a magnificent looking modern building I
really like that
we gotta go we gotta do it
Boop
and I didn't get the point for that
adding ah
really I don't think the point system's
working
he knows what's up
he knows what I've just done
I did just get him though so even though
I didn't go on the counter I definitely
got the point there I've just told scar
that this place looks absolutely amazing
and that snowball had his name on it
anyway I think that's where we're going
to leave today's episode as the the sun
sets and I'm here with scar my dude
yeah it's been a fantastic episode I did
have I did spend a lot of time
um working with Poetry Man to make that
little cinematic and building his his
cave so that was a lot of fun and then
we made a little entrance for it using
our fantastic Redstone skills and next
episode maybe poultry man will make a
true appearance alright thank you very
much for watching everyone please let me
know what you thought about today's
episode in the comments below and good
bye